从三岁起 我就梦想着和我的偶像伊莱·曼宁一样
Ever since I was 3, I wanted to play quarterback for the New York Giants,
在纽约巨人队打四分卫
like my personal hero, Eli Manning.
年薪在一千万到两千万之间
Annual salary is between 10 and 20 million dollars a year.
谢谢
Thank you.
下一个是...里德
Next up... Reed?
理查兹先生
Mr. Richards.
到你了 理查兹
Earth to Richards.
把我传送回去吧 斯科特
Beam me up, Scotty.
- 好了好了 同学们 - 对不起
- Okay, come on guys. - Oh, sorry.
奥伊斯特贝, 纽约    2007
等我长大了
When I grow up,
我要做人类历史上第一个用时空传送自己的人
I want to be the first person in human history to teleport himself.
不好意思 你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
从一个地方向另一个地方传送量子信息已经成为可能
It's already possible to transport quantum information from one location to another.
现在 又有超级电脑可以
Right now, there are supercomputers that can transport
向太空中传送量子信息
quantum information through space,
所以为什么就不能有机器把人类传送到外太空呢
so why not a machine that can send people through space?
好吧 即使你可以造出这种东西 当然你造不出
Well, even if you could build the thing, which you can't.
我已经造出来了
I've already built it.
好吧 我正在造 在我的车库里
Well, I'm building it. In my garage.
所以是就在你的小飞车旁边吗
Is it next to your flying car?
那台车我已经不研究了 现在我只研究这台机器
I'm not working on that anymore. Just this now.
- 我叫它 生物质能穿梭器 - 生物质能...
- I call it, The Biomatter Shuttle. - Biomatter...
基本上来说 就是我要把物质从一个地方传送到另一个地方
Technically, I'm shuttling matter from one place to another.
首先 物质
Well. First, matter.
一旦我试过生物材料 我就可以...
But once I test on biological materials, I can...
好了 非常感谢你 理查兹先生
Alright. Well. thank you, Mr. Richards,
你说的都很有趣 但是我们的作业
This is all very interesting, but the assignment
是在现实世界中选一个真实的职业来完成
was to pick a real career in the real world.
重做报告吧 明天我会让你再说一次
Redo the report and I'll let you try again tomorrow.
本
Ben?
这姑娘现在跟我住在一起 你想怎样
The girl is living with me, so what're you going to do about it.?
那是谁
What was that?
- 嘿 你去哪 - 我有作业要写
- Hey, where you going? - I got homework.
什么 你看看那边堆成山的废旧冰箱
What? Look at that fridge pile.
- 白痴 - 你说什么
- Idiot. - What'd you say?
嘿 胖揍时间到了
Hey! Clobberin' time.
过来 你想什么呢
Come here. What'd you think?
竟敢这么跟我说话
You think you can talk to me like that?
你以为你可以这样跟我说话吗
Huh! You think you can talk to me like that?
- 废物 我要打... - 你到底有什么毛病
- Punk, I ought to beat... - What the hell's the matter with you?
靠
Shit.
妈妈
Ma.
我什么都没做
I didn't do nothing.
- 妈妈 我发誓 - 你什么也没做
- Ma, I swear to god. - You didn't do nothing.
你去看看后面什么动静
Go check on that fuss.
你什么也没做吗 我可什么都看见了
You didn't do nothing? I watched you.
你到底怎么回事 我还要跟你说多少遍
What's the matter with you? How many times do I have to tell you,
- 不许打小孩子 - 妈妈 拜托别这样
- you don't hit a kid. - Ma, please.
嘿
Hey!
有人吗
Hello?
谁在里面
Who's in there?
拜托别杀我
Please don't kill me.
把帽子摘下来
Take that off.
我在学校里见过你
I know you, from school.
我只是在找一个整流器
I'm just looking for a power converter.
我在做东西
I'm building something.
- 本 你那边怎么样了 - 等一下
- Ben! What's going on out there? - Hold on!
是时空传送的那个吗
That teleporting thing?
我可以给你看 我只是需要一个整流器
I can show it to you. I just need the converter.
好吧
All right.
快点 投球啊
Come on, throw the ball!
扔过去 扔过去
Throw the ball. Throw the ball.
德怀特那里空了 快扔过去啊
Dwlight is open, throw the ball!
- 就是那个吗 - 是的
- That it? - Yeah.
帮我一下
Help... me.
给你
Here you go.
那个回收站是你家的吗
Your family owns a junkyard?
嗯
Mm-hm.
那地方棒呆了
That place is awesome.
给你这个 用这个头来拆
Here, you're stripping the head.
所以 还有谁住这儿么
So. Who else lives here?
就我妈妈 还有我继父
Just my mom and stepdad.
他们不介意这些东西吗
They don't care about all this?
他们根本不懂
They don't understand it.
你最好把耳朵捂上
You might want to cover your ears.
往后站一点儿
Stand back a little.
搞什么 该死的
What the hell? Damn it.
没事的 好了 好了 继续
It's alright. Alright, alright, play on.
千万别爆炸
Don't blow up.
千万别爆炸啊
加油啊 那个人没人防啊
Come on, man! The guy's open!
哦 里德 你干了什么
Whoa! Reed, what did you do?
就是现在
Now!
里德
Reed!
成功了吗
Did it work?
这些石头哪里来的
Where the rocks come from?
从这辆车传送去的那个地方吧
From the same place the car went to.
那是哪儿
Where is that?
我也不知道
I don't know yet.
里德
Reed.
怎么了
What?
你疯了
You're insane.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
七年后
理查兹先生
Mr. Richards.
我是不是要先通知一下消防队
Shall I alert the fire department?
这是什么
What is this?
这是一个声波具象化物质传送机
Uh, this is a Cymatic Matter Shuttle.
我和我的助手本自从五年级在我家车库
Uh, me and my associate, Ben, have been working on it
完成了测试版以后 就一直在研究这个
every day since fifth grade when we launched the beta version in my garage.
今天是我们第一次公开展示
And today is our first public demonstration.
它能干什么
What does it do?
它可以通过调节物体的频率把它在两个地点之间进行传送
It modulates the frequency of matter from one location to another and back again.
- 这是一个传送门 - 传送门
- It's a teleporter. - A teleporter.
把模型车给我
Model car, please.
模型车 那辆模型车给我啊 本
The model... the model car, please, Ben.
- 我没带那辆车 -你为什么不带模型车啊
- I don't have the model car. - Why don't you have the model car?
- 我以为我把该带的都带了 - 我有特别跟你说啊
- I thought I brought everything. - I specifically said.
发生了什么 理查兹先生
What? Mr. Richards?
好吧 那我用这架模型飞机
Okay, I will use this model plane.
嘿 我只要借用...一下就可以了
Hey, I just need to use this for... one second,
我保证然后我会它还回来的 谢谢
but I'll give it back. I promise, thanks.
来吧
Here we go.
本 开始吧
Ben. Please.
你最好把耳朵捂上
You may want to cover your ears.
- 非常好 现在 本 把它弄回来 - 好的
- Great. Now Ben, bring it on back. - Yeah.
- 哦 继续捂着吧 - 好了 我们继续
- Oh, keep them covered. - All right, come on.
拜托 别这样
Come on. Don't do this.
哦 好了
Oh! Okay.
现在 请听我讲解
Now if I can have your attention please.
各位现在看到的 可能是中国甘肃沙漠中的沙子
What you're looking at, is sand presumably from the Gansu desert in China,
- 或者是撒哈拉沙漠的 - 你被取消资格了
- or perhaps even from the Sahara. - You're disqualified.
- 我们还不完全确定 - 理查兹先生
- We're not entirely sure. - Mr. Richards.
- 怎么了 - 你被取消资格了
- Yeah? - You're disqualified.
等一等 什么
Wait, what?
这是一个科学讨论会 不是一个魔术比赛
This is a science fair not a magic competition.
我在这找不到任何科学性可言
I don't see any real science here.
而且你还要赔偿篮板的损失
And you're paying for the backboard.
- 你有把它放在传感器里吗 - 和之前一样啊
- Did you put in the sensors? - Everything is the same.
我知道 但你砸按钮了 它很脆弱的 你不能用砸的
I know, but your smashing the buttons. It's delicate, you can't smash it.
嘿 小弟弟 我很抱歉弄坏了你的飞机
Hey, kid, I'm really sorry about your plane.
你个混蛋
You're a dick.
- 你把手柄转的太高了 - 我没有转的太高
- You cranked it up too high. - I didn't crank it up too high.
这和刚开始的所有设定是一样的
It's on the same settings as the first time.
它非常 我知道它非常精细
It's very... I know it's very precise.
- 不好意思 我可以... - 把它装起来吧
- Excuse me, but, could I... - Just pack it up.
怎么了
Yeah?
你真的是在车库里造出这个的吗
Did you really build this in your garage?
嗯
Mm-hm.
这东西真是太漂亮了
Now this is elegant.
这些是什么
What are these?
用可视声波来调节燃料的声波投影仪
Um, sonic projectors using cymatics to modulate the fuel.
这就是为什么我们没法从另一个维度把物质带回来的原因
That's why we can't bring the matter back from the other dimension.
什么
Uh, what?
我们已经可以做到把物质送到另一个维度
We've gone so far as to send matter to another dimension but we haven't
但是还做不到让燃料可以撑到把物质带回来
been able to maintain the fuel long enough to bring that matter back.
但你做到了
You just did.
哦 你是认真的吗
Oh, you're serious?
我觉得你破解了跨纬度旅行这个难题
I think you've cracked inter-dimensional travel.
啊 我觉得 我们没有把东西送到另一个维度
Ah, I mean, we're not... we're not sending anything to another dimension,
我以为我们只是把它们送去了地球上的另一个地方
we send something, we think, to another part of the planet
但我不知道还有另一个维度这件事
but, I don't know about another dimension.
我们也找到了跟你们一样的东西
We found the same thing you did.
我们反复分析过
We've had it analyzed repeatedly, but
但是地球上没有人见过这种物质
no one's ever seen anything like it.
哇哦
Oh wow.
不好意思 我们来自巴克斯特基金会
I'm sorry, we're from the Baxter Foundation.
这是我女儿 苏
This is my daughter, Sue.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hey.
我们想给你提供全额奖学金
We like to give you a full scholarship.
呃 你刚刚说你是哪个机构的来着
Uh, where did you say you were from again?
嘿
Hey.
我们一整个小区的人搬进那里都没问题吧
They could put the whole neighborhood in there.
巴克斯特
- 你叫什么名字 - 里德
- What's your name? - Uh, Reed.
理查兹 真是你 我们等你很久了
Richards! Yes, of course, we've been expecting you.
他们在这真的都穿着白大褂呢
They actually wear lab coats here.
这是你们的房间 先生
This is you, sir.
- 给你 - 什么
- Here. - What?
这是什么
What is this?
这是一份远行礼物
It's a going away present.
我又不是远行 我只是在离奥伊斯特贝四十分钟火车的地方
I'm not going away, I'm, like, a 40 minute train ride from Oyster Bay.
里德 看看这地方
Reed, look at this place.
你属于这里 虽然我才来两分钟 但我知道
You belong here, I've been here 2 minutes and I already know that.
我只是在这里上学 以后在这里工作而已
I'm just going to school here, it's where I'm going to be working.
这里看上去才是你的家 兄弟
It looks like you're home, buddy.
巴克斯特的研究者证明了暗物质的存在
巴克斯特学院开发了第一个四核系列的超级芯片
嘿
Hey.
这地方太棒了 他们有上世纪50年代的分子化学书
This place is pretty incredible, they have molecular chem books from the 1950s.
不好意思 你说什么
Oh, hey. Sorry, did you say something?
我在问... 你在听什么呢
Yeah, I was just asking, uh... what are you listening to?
波蒂斯黑德
Portishead.
- 没听说过他 - 是他们
- Never heard of him. - Them.
我回去查查他们
I'll have to check them out.
我超爱这本书
I love this book.
讲了一个叫尼莫船长的人
It's about this guy, Captain Nemo,
他发明了一艘史上潜的最深的潜水艇
he invents a submarine that goes deeper than anything in history.
我知道 我读过
Yeah, I know. I read it.
所以你喜欢音乐吗 你的爱好吗
So you like music? Is that, kinda like, your thing?
- 一种模式识别罢了 - 模式识别
- Pattern recognition. - Pattern recognition?
音乐就是一系列变化的模式
Music is just a series of altered patterns.
音乐家创造出这些模式 并让我们对后续进行预测
The musician creates the pattern and makes us anticipate a resolution
然后控制他 让你为之期待
and holds back, makes you wait for it.
每件事 每个人都有自己的模式
There's patterns in everything and everyone.
那我的模式呢
Hmm. What's mine?
你想出名
You want to be famous.
你的父母老师 所有人都只告诉你一条路 但是
Your parents, teachers, all told you one thing, one way to be, and
- 你无视了他们 - 然后我就在这儿了
- you ignored them. - And now I'm here.
是啊
So you are.
我真那么好猜吗?
Am I that predictable?
每个人都是
Everybody is.
但你错了 我并不想成名
Well, you're wrong, I don't want to be famous.
我只是希望我所做的事情能改变点什么
I just want my work to make a difference.
所以你在这了 尼莫船长
Well here you are, Captain Nemo.
加油
Go for it.
再见
Bye.
让我猜猜 是网络上的某个小屁孩
Let me guess, some kid from the internet.
是科学博览会
Science fair.
富兰克林 董事会已经给你的"小孤儿院"投了很多钱了
Franklin, this board has invested a great deal in your little orphanage.
- 我们需要些实际的能运用的成果 - 这个项目有能运用的成果
- We need real world applications. - This has real world applications.
我十分确信存在着一个完全...
I truly believe that there is an entirely...
一个完全超越我们可视能力的全新时空
An entirely new universe just beyond our ability to see.
是的 我读过你的文章
Yes, I read your paper.
- 一旦我们到达那里 - 如果我们到达那里
- Once we get there - If we get there.
我们将找到新的资源和能源
We'll be able to discover new resources,
这样地球上的一切就可以得到恢复
energy sources, which will revitalize our own.
这是我们机会去更深入了解 甚至可能拯救我们的星球
This is our chance to learn more about our planet and maybe even save it.
我相信你们都会同意哪怕...
And I'm sure you all would agree that even if such a...
等等 这是什么
Wait, what is this?
维克多·冯·杜姆在名单上
Victor Von Doom is on here.
他开创了这个项目并且投入了十年的岁月在其中
He started this project and devoted a decade of his life to it.
- 他该进监狱 - 应该再给他一次机会
- He deserves to be in jail. - He deserves another chance.
他离开之前烧了你们的数据服务器
He set fire to your data servers before he left.
我会亲自监督他
I'm going to personally supervise him.
我需要他的天赋
I need his talent.
我相信他和里德最终能把我们带到那里
I believe he and Reed can finally get us there.
富兰克林 我们想支持你 但你过于信任这些孩子了
We want to support you Franklin, but you put a lot of faith in these kids.
我完全相信他们
I put all my faith in them.
所以说 有人窃取了我的设计
So someone stole my design.
没有谁窃取什么 维克托
No one stole anything, Victor.
另一个人也想出了你的点子并且使之实现了
Someone else figured out your idea and made it worked.
这就是在你远离尘世时发生的事
That's what happens when you drop out of the world.
别人完成了你开创的想法
Other people finish what you started.
如果你是想来寻求帮助
Well, if you came to ask for help,
你最好不要自取其辱就这么走吧
it'd be better you didn't insult both of us and turned back around.
你都不想看看那个设计吗?
Don't you want to even look at the designs?
我说过我不再为你和你的雇主工作了
I told you I'm done working for you and your employers.
他们不是我的雇主
They're not my employers.
没他们的允许 你什么也不能做 对吧?
You can't do a thing without their permission, yes?
醒醒吧 你就是个打工的
Wake up, you're an employee.
相信我 他们这次不会干涉我的
They'll stay out of my way this time, trust me.
我不是不相信你
It's not you I don't trust.
好吧
Well.
那我就不打扰你那些重要的工作了
I hate to interfere with all your important work.
也许我们就只能在没有你的情况下创造历史了
Guess we'll just have to make history without you.
苏也会去吗?
Is Sue going to be there?
我相信她
I trust her.
是的 维克托 她会在那儿
Yes Victor, she'll be there.
收拾干净自己 孩子
Clean yourself up, son.
天啊
Holy shit.
真令人吃惊!
Amazing.
谢谢
Thanks.
真令人吃惊你竟然没把整个西半球弄停电
Amazing you didn't black out the entire western hemisphere.
嗯?
Hmm?
简单来说 你使用非指定的元件并在没有监督的情况下
You basically ripped a hole in the fabric of space-time
把空间时间结构体给撕开了一个洞
with unspec'd components and no supervision.
好吧 那是... 个意外
Yeah, that was... an accident.
如果你"意外地"提高了功率 你很可能会造成反应失控
And if by accident you upped the power you would have created a run-away reaction
而那会生成一个黑洞 吞噬掉整个地球
that opened a black hole and swallowed the entire planet.
好吧 我很庆幸那并没有发生
Well, I'm glad that didn't happen.
你是来帮忙解决这个问题的?
Are you helping on this?
我来准备适应外界环境的衣服的
I'm making the environment suits.
根据我们在实验中获得的土壤样本
Based on the soil samples from our experiments,
所有去那个异度空间的任何人都需要保护措施
anyone who goes to the other dimension is going to need to be protected.
那个人是谁?
Who's that?
维克托
Victor.
谁是维克托?
Who's Victor?
他开创了这个项目
He started this whole project.
哦 他也会来儿咯?
Oh. Does he go here too?
不好说
It's complicated.
太不成熟了
Rudimentary.
太初级了
Elementary.
基本上来说这就是小孩子画的画
It's basically a child's drawing.
你知道 阿尔伯特爱因斯坦说过的
You know what Albert Einstein said.
如果你不能简单解释一件事情 那么你就是你没理解清楚
If you can't explain it simply, you don't understand it well enough.
十年的寻寻觅觅结果是个
10 years searching for something that is
凭火山喷发模型拿到亚军的人
basically runner-up for a baking soda volcano.
其实我们被取消了资格 土豆时钟拿了亚军
We were actually disqualified. The potato clock got second.
里德·理查斯 维克多·冯·杜姆
Reed Richards, Victor Von Doom.
维克托在比你还年轻的时候开创了量子门项目
Victor started the Quantum Gate project when he was younger than you.
见到你真高兴
Well, it's great to meet you.
- 你好 苏珊- 你好 维克托
- Hi Susan. - Hey Victor.
- 你更喜欢被叫成苏珊? - 不 曾经这么叫过
- Do you prefer Susan? - No. It's been awhile.
我没想到你还会回来
I didn't expect to see you back here.
好吧 我无法拒绝呢
Yeah, well I couldn't resist.
当我听说这个设计以后 我需要亲眼看看
When I heard about the design I needed to see it with my own eyes.
- 我不得不说这东西真的挺印象深刻的... - 谢谢
- I gotta say it's pretty impressive... - Thank you.
你差点用音箱线和铝箔
That you nearly destroyed an entire planet
毁了整个地球
with speaker cable and aluminum foil.
- 是 是有点意外 - 他的确成功了
- Yeah, that was an accident. - He did get it to work.
这是什么?
What is this?
这是你的小意外指向的地方
This is where your little, accident leads to.
我们在送过去的无人机上装了摄像机
We put a camera on a drone we sent over there,
无人机没回来但那些照片传回来了
the drone didn't come back but those images did.
哇 真漂亮
Wow. It's beautiful.
是的 新的能量 资源 那是个全新的世界
Yes it is. New energy, resources. It's a whole new world.
它可以拯救地球
Which can help save this one.
它不值得被拯救
Not that it deserves to be saved.
我是说想想看
I mean think about it,
主宰地球的人类也正是使地球衰败的主犯
the people running the earth are the same ones running it into the ground
所以也许地球理应遭受正在经历的这一切
so maybe it deserves what it's got coming to it.
就像这里的杜姆博士
Like Dr. Doom over here.
我们这一代的失败是你们的机会
The failures of my generation are the opportunities for yours.
没有人比这间屋子里的人更聪明了
There are no greater minds than the ones in this room.
- 他又要开始演讲了吗? - 他要开始演讲了
- Is he going to give a speech? - He's going to give a speech.
不过你们要联合起来
But you're going to have to all come together.
如果你们想修复我们这代人对地球造成的伤害的话
Each of you working together with a level of commitment
就要大家一起在达成共识的角度上
and collaboration, putting aside petty squabbles,
把分歧放在一边 通力合作
if you want to fix what my generation broke.
如果你们可以做到 一起努力
If you can do that, work together,
然后你们将改变历史的轨迹
then you can change the course of history.
真是个精彩的演讲
That's a pretty good speech.
算我一个
I'm in.
我也是 我已经在这了 不是吗?
Me too. I'm here, right?
首先 设计
First, design.
我们要找出设计的不足之处并将其改正
We figure out what went wrong and correct it.
然后我们建造实物 再运送有机物质去那儿
Then we build, then we send organic matter over there.
然而更重要的是 我们要把它再传回来
But more importantly, we bring it back.
然后 重中之重 它们要把我们送过去
And then, most importantly, they send us.
我们?
Us?
"我们" 我们?
"Us" us?
我们要去那里吗?
We're going over there?
要实现你们就得开始工作
Not unless you get to work.
所以 工作去吧
So get to work.
老爸来电
约翰尼·斯通.
Johnny Storm
这就是你一直在说的那辆破丰田
So that's the piece of shit Toyota you been talking about.
是的 就是它
Well, yes it is.
你答应我 在我把你甩到后面以后 我们还能这样谈笑风生
Now you promise me, we'll still be cool after I dust your ass.
不是吧
No.
快啊
Come on.
菜鸟
Rookie!
再见
Bye bye.
我真不敢相信你又在外面干这么没意义的事情
I cannot believe you are out here doing this nonsense again.
我跟你说过了的
I told you.
什么
What?
我跟你说了我出事的时候只开了四十五迈
I told you I was doing 45 when I spun out.
地面是湿的 我打滑了
The ground was wet and I hydroplaned.
真好笑 我好像不记得今天有下雨
Funny, I don't seem to remember any rain today.
你可能太忙了没注意到
You were probably too busy to notice.
约翰尼！
Johnny!
我以为你在改变 这是在搞什么?
I thought you were turning things around, what is this?
- 你在说什么? - 这 这些
- What are you talking about? - This, this!
这就是你所希望的今后生活的方式吗?
Is this the way you want the rest of your life to be?
你一直没做正事 凭你的潜力还有的智商 你可以做得更好
You keep acting out. You have the potential and the IQ to do so much more.
你的意思是像苏一样吗?
Oh you mean like Sue?
我知道你以为你知道什么对你是最好的 但儿子相信我 你不明白
I know you think you know what's best for you but trust me son you do not.
- 你能停下来吗? - 什么? 停下什么?
- Can you stop that? - What? Stop what?
别再把我当你的学生一样的训斥
Stop talking to me like I'm one of your students.
- 好吧 车子你别想拿回去了 - 什么?
- Well you're not getting the car back. - Excuse me?
车子你别想拿回去了
You're not getting the car back.
那是我亲手从草图开始一点点做出来的
I built that thing from scratch with my own two hands.
用我的钱
With my money.
我的钱 所以是我的车
My money, my car.
你想要回你的车 那你就得把它赚回来
You want it back, you're gonna have to earn it.
你得来为我工作
You're gonna have to come work for me.
我才不要穿实验室工作服
I'm not wearing a lab coat.
我很确定你并没错过什么
I'm pretty sure you weren't missed.
哦 你得把那衬衣扯出来 伙计
Oh. You got to untuck that shirt, man.
那是... 阿道夫?
Is that... Adolph?
好久不见
Long time.
我并不是德国人 而且 我们不需要任何帮助了
I'm still not German. And, we don't need any more help.
不 你们需要
Yes you do.
需要什么 他无限的热情吗?
With what, his boundless enthusiasm?
哦 干嘛这样 谢谢夸奖 维克托
Oh, why, thank you, Victor.
他可以做出任何东西
He can build anything.
在断了的胳膊的情况下
With a broken arm.
- 到底发生什么了? - 什么?
- What exactly happened? - What?
- 你又去赛车了? - 我不知道你在说什么
- Were you racing again? - I don't know what you're talking about.
其实 我需要点帮助
I could use some help, actually.
哦 这家伙接活儿可不怎么靠谱
Oh this guy doesn't take orders well.
是 尤其是对那些说我接单不靠谱的人来说
Yeah, especially from people who say shit like I don't take orders well.
- 你需要什么 伙计? - 哦 那真是不错
- What you need, buddy? - Oh, that's brilliant.
- 你好 - 嘿
- What's up? - Hey.
- 约翰尼 - 里德 很高兴见到你
- Johnny. - Reed. Nice to meet you.
- 你之前做过焊接吗? - 当然
- Have you welded before? - Of course.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了?
What's up?
我不得不说 有你在这还挺有趣的
I gotta say, it's fun having you here.
你看起来还挺在状态的
You kinda look like you're in your element.
听着 别习惯这样
Look, don't get used to this.
我来这只是为了拿回我的车
I'm just here to get my car back.
好吧
Right.
不过见到你也蛮开心的
It's good seeing you too.
格林姆回收站
- 快搞定了! - 兄弟 若是没有你 我肯定搞不定啊!
- 啊呀 - 抱歉
- Oh. - Sorry.
我的天
Oh my god.
- 你干嘛要这样 - 不好意思
- Why did you do that? - Sorry.
吓了我一跳 我刚才... 抱歉
I freak out like that, I was like... sorry.
你刚刚是在打盹哦
You were sort of sleeping.
是吗 我睡着了呀
Was I? Is that what that was?
你要是需要打个盹什么的 完全没问题啊
It's okay if you need to take a nap or something.
不用 我很好 谢谢
No, I'm good, thanks.
有个斯通博士这样的老爸
So. That must have been
一定很酷吧
cool with... Dr. Storm as your dad.
当然
Yeah.
你是被他领养的吗
Did he adopt you?
嗯
Mm-hm.
我了解那是什么感觉
Yeah, I know what that's like.
你也是被领养的吗
You were adopted?
不 但我倒希望我是被领养的
No, I-I just wish that I was.
- 为什么 - 不知道
- Why? - I don't know, I just,
我们其实一点都不了解对方
we don't really understand each other.
你在哪出生的
Where were you born?
- 科索沃 - 科索沃哦
- Kosovo. - Kosovo.
你说话都没口音呢
You don't have an accent.
是吗
I don't?
嘿 里德 我能和你聊几句吗
Hey, Reed. Can I have a word?
好的
Okay. Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
你这样太不专业了
You're being unprofessional.
你来这儿是工作的
You're supposed to be down here working.
是啊 的确 我就是在工作啊
Yeah, I am. That's what we've been doing.
看起来可不像啊
That's not what it looks like.
我们已经搞定了
We're finished.
什么
What?
我们搞定了 你想看看吗
Yeah, we, we finished it. Do you want to see?
好
Yeah.
嘿 苏
Hey Sue.
能演示给他看看嘛
Can you show him?
我真的累死了 我要去小睡一会儿
I'm really tired, I'm going to go take a nap.
能帮我带给斯通博士打个招呼嘛
Can you tell Dr. Storm for me?
我们做到了 维克托
We did it Victor.
- 哈维 - 富兰克林
- Harvey. - Franklin.
今天真是个大日子啊
Big day.
没想到我们就这么成功了 但 干得不错
Didn't think we'd make it here, but, well done.
我告诉过你这些孩子能做到的
I told you these kids could do it.
哈维来了
Harvey's here.
生命体测试开始
Organic test commencing.
准备发射
Clear for launch.
请戴好眼镜
Goggles up.
十
10.
九
9.
八
8.
七
7.
六
6.
五
5.
四
4.
三
3.
二
2.
一
1.
- 哇哦 - 太棒了
- Woo! - Alright!
准备接收视频
Standing by for video on position.
未知状态  待机
Status unknown, stand by.
启动备用频率
Trying an alternate frequency.
我们有信号了
We've got signal.
快看这些板块啊 几乎都处于原始形态
Look at the plates, it's almost primordial.
还未成形 就像是十亿多年前的地球
Unformed, like Earth over a billion years ago.
这地方也许可以解释我们的物种起源
That place could explain the origin of our species.
解释我们星球的进化
The evolution of our planet,
回答那些我们甚至都还没有探寻过的问题
answers to questions we don't even know to ask yet.
应急电源 体温和通风率都升高了
EPS, body temp, ventilation rates are all elevated.
让他回来吧
Let's bring him back.
开始返回
SHUTTLE RETURN INITIATED
请戴好眼镜
Goggles up.
将于五秒内启动
In 5.
四
4.
三
3.
二
2.
一
1.
他还好吗
How is he?
生命体征一切正常
The vitals are good.
身体情况非常好
They're really good.
他成功了
He made it.
安全完成实验
It's safe.
很好
All right.
看上去接下来就轮到我们了
Looks like we're next.
先生们
Gentlemen.
大家好
Everyone.
你们都应受到表扬
You all deserve an enormous pat on the back.
我想是时候同我们航空航天局的朋友们一起合作了
I think it's time to start coordinating with our friends at NASA.
什么
What?
这很成功 我们要开始考虑把人类送上去
It works. We have to start thinking about sending men.
对啊
Yeah.
就是把我们送上去啊
Us.
我要承认你们创造出来的这些成果的确令人难以置信
Look, I won't deny that what you've created here is incredible.
但这不是学校里的科学展览
But this isn't the school science fair anymore.
我们必须让它派上真正的用场
We have to bring in help now.
嘿 为什么是航空航天局 为什么不是军队或者中央情报局
Well, hey, why just NASA? Why not the Army, or the CIA?
我们可以把政治犯送过去
We could send our political prisoners there,
水刑在第四维度里很可能是非常有效的哦
waterboarding in the 4th dimension could prove very effective.
不如我们换个地方再讨论这些细节吧
Why don't we discuss the details of this someplace else?
同时 我们对你们的贡献表示衷心地感谢
In the meantime, we appreciate your service.
嘿 谢谢你全家
Oh, hey, thank you.
我不会善罢甘休的 我保证
I won't let this go, I promise you.
给他点时间想明白吧
Just give him a second to figure this out.
我对你们这些人都不了解 但...
Look, I don't know about you guys, but...
我可以想点办法
I could use some.
来喝一杯吧
one drink.
酒精会扼杀脑细胞的
Ethanol kills brain cells.
哈哈 你酒量好怂啊
Heh heh. You are a light-weight.
看来我们要再来一瓶了
Looks like we need another refill.
嘿 维克
Hey Vic.
你们知道阿波罗号飞船是谁造出来 送上月球的吗
You guys know who built the Apollo spacecraft, went to the moon?
当然 你老妈吧
Yeah. Your mama.
所以没人知道咯
So the answer's no?
但你们都知道尼尔·阿姆斯特朗 对吧
But you know who Neil Armstrong is, right?
- 对 当然 - 当然
- Oh, yeah, of course. - Of course.
尼尔·阿姆斯特朗和巴兹·奥尔德林都参加了
第一次载人登月计划
乘坐阿波罗11号登上月球
- 还有巴兹·奥尔德林 - 知道
- Buzz Aldrin. - Yeah.
首次在月球上行走的两个人
First men to walk on the moon.
他们这些名人无非是被雇来 征服那些根本就不是他们自己的梦想
Famous faces hired to conquer dreams that weren't even theirs.
那是别人的梦想 那是其他科学家的梦想
Dreams of someone else, some other scientist
而那些科学家们可能最终身无分文 孤苦伶仃
who probably died penniless and alone
只能坐在酒吧里告诉人们他曾经还送过人类上过月球
and sat in a bar telling people he sent men to the moon.
说的不就是我吗
That's going to be me.
说的也是我
That's gonna be me.
我想我们都一样
I think it's all of us.
除非我们先行一步
Unless we go first.
我们为什么不先行一步呢
Why don't we go first?
天呐 这个装置运转得挺好的 不是吗
My God. This thing works. Okay?
我们可以先上去 花个五分钟
We can go up there, take 5 minutes,
我们可以带上旗子 插在那 在那留下我们的足迹
we could take a flag, plant it down, get our footprints down there,
我们可以成为第一次登上那里的人 对吗 让他们见鬼去吧
we're going to be the first people over there, okay? Screw those guys.
这一次我爸可能真要杀了我了
My dad might actually kill me this time.
约翰尼 等你老爸发现的时候 我们都已经回来了
Johnny, by the time your dad finds out, we'll already be back.
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
就我们三个去吗
Just the 3 of us?
- 哪位 - 你不来我是不会去的
- Hello? - I'm not going without you.
现在几点了
What time is it?
听着 是我们俩一起开始做这个项目的 那我们要继续一起
Look, we started this thing together, we're going together,
你不能拒绝我 好嘛
I'm not taking "No" for an answer, okay?
忘了尼尔·阿姆斯特朗 来吧
Forget Neil Armstrong! Come on.
尼尔·阿姆斯特朗
Neil Armstrong?
- 你喝多了 - 对 我是喝的有点多
- You're drunk. - Yeah, I am a little drunk.
这不重要 重要的是机器成功了
It doesn't matter. Look, the machine works.
那机器成功了 本 我要你和我一起去
The machine works, Ben, and I need you to come with me.
现在吗
Now?
对
Yeah.
本 我需要你去 因为我们准备今晚出发 而且我和他们说了
Look, Ben, I need you to come, because we're going tonight and I told the guys
你不来的话 我是不会去的
that I'm not going without you.
可以吗 谁会挺我到底呢
Okay? Who's going to have my back?
好吧 可以 那等我一会 可以吗
Alright, fine. Just-Just give me a second, alright?
- 好 - 等一会 好吗
- Okay. - Please, all right?
- 好的 兄弟 - 谢了
- All right, buddy. - Thank you.
他和我是一起的
He's with me.
- 啊! - 嘿 伙计
- Ah! - Hey what's up man.
- 你好 伙计 - 你还好吗 朋友
- What's up buddy. - How you doing, man.
见到你真好 谢了 帕诺
Good to see you. Thanks, Pano.
不客气 理查兹先生
No problem, Mr. Richards.
- 为什么我们要今晚出发 - 啊
- Why are we doing this tonight? - Huh?
我们为什么要今晚出发
Why are we doing this tonight?
你信的过我 对吧
You trust me, right?
跟我们那个很像 就是贵了点
It's just like ours, but expensive.
伙计们
Guys.
这是本
This is Ben.
你们好
How you're doing.
- 你好 - 你就是他的护身符吗
- What's up. - You're his lucky charm?
抱歉 这位是波拉特 他就是个混蛋
I'm sorry, this is Borat. Borat's a dick.
你们确定现在处于最佳状态吗
You guys sure you're in the best shape to be doing this?
- 当然 - 是的
- Oh yeah. - Yeah.
我们没问题的
We're good.
我们开始吧
Let's do this.
所以我要想出一句比"我个人的一小步"
So I guess I should come up with something better than
我个人的一小步
是尼尔·阿姆斯特朗在首次踏上月球时所说的一句话
全句为:这是我个人的一小步,却是人类的一大步
更棒的话
"One small step for man?"
系好安全带 放松点 孩子 我们要书写历史了
Strap in and get comfy, kids. We're about to make history.
对 或者我们也会挂掉 二者必居其一
Yeah, or die. Either or.
哇哦 那可真不错 本 谢了
Wow. That's great, Ben. Thanks.
好了 先生们
All right, gentlemen.
在这次旅途中 手脚必须时刻保持在装备里
Hands and feet must remain inside the ride at all times.
[量子门活跃]
[ QUANTUM GATE ACTIVE ]
该死
Shit.
爸爸你快来趟实验室
Dad you need to come to the lab.
远程启动开启
REMOTE LAUNCH INITIATED
十
10.
- 千万别爆炸 - 九
- Don't blow up. - 9.
拜托了 别爆炸
Please, don't blow up.
你狠 我在进入另一个维度前就想听你说这些
Oh yeah, that's what I want to hear before going into another dimension.
别担心 他就这样
Yeah. Don't worry, he does that.
五
5.
四
4.
三
3.
二
2.
一
1.
准备发射
Initiate launch.
怎么了
What happened?R
我们到了吗
Did we abort?
呃 我觉得我们哪也没去成
Uh, I don't think that we went anywhere.
该死
God damn it.
约翰尼
Johnny?
你们能听到我吗
Guys, can you hear me?
我成功了
I made it.
本
Ben.
看看这地方
Look at this place.
太神奇了
It's amazing.
我们做到了
We did it.
我们成功了
I think we did.
- 来 帮我一下 - 好的
- Here, give me a hand. - Yeah.
太棒了 我一定要把这个传到社交网站上去
Oh yeah, this one is definitely going on Instagram.
好了 让我们把旗子插上 准备好了吗
All right, let's do this. Ready?
我数到三 一 二 三
After 3. 1, 2, 3.
- 哇 看看这 - 哇
- Woo! Look at that. - Whoa.
维克托 我觉得你应该看看这个
Hey Victor. I think you should see this.
能量似乎都汇聚到那边去了
The energy seems to be converging over there.
来 一起去看看
Come on. Let's check it out.
好了 赶紧的 完事就走
Alright. Well, let's do it quickly, so we can get out of here.
不是吧
Nope. Uh-uh.
算了吧
I'm good.
里德 他在干什么
Reed. What's he doing?
我们要爬下去 才能找到一个更好的观测视角
We need to climb down there so we can get a better look.
你们去吧
Oh, you guys go on without me.
你待这吧 我们需要有人压阵
Stay here. We need an anchor.
好 好 我一定会好好看着的
Yeah. Yeah, yeah I'll be a great anchor.
慢慢来
Easy does it.
再往前走远点
Just a little further.
我们就在你身后
Right behind you.
好了
Okay.
这东西对物理刺激有反应 就像神经脉冲
It's responding to physical stimulus, almost like a nerve impulse.
我能感受到它
I can feel it.
这能量 是有生命的
The energy, it's alive.
真是令人难以置信
It's incredible.
这没有能量损耗
There's no expenditure.
- 里德 - 怎么了
- Reed. - What?
我觉得我们应该回去了
I think we should go back.
这事关紧要 本 快过来看
This is important, Ben. Come take a look.
起来 快跑
Get up! Come on!
- 小心 - 快走
- Look out! - Come on!
快 快 快 赶紧的
Come on. Come on. Come on. Hurry up.
加油 里德 快
Come on Reed, come on!
维克托
Victor!
- 里德 - 坚持住
- Reed! - Hold on!
- 里德 拉我上去 - 维克托
- Reed pull me up! - Victor!
抓住我的手
Grab my hand!
里德 拉我上去
Reed! Pull me up!
加油 加油
Come on. Come on.
维克托 坚持住
Victor hold on!
- 里德! 我抓不住了 - 别放手
- Reed! I can't hold it! - Don't let go!
救救我
Help me!
不 维克托
No, Victor!
维克托 不
Victor! No!
里德 快走 快
Reed! Let's go, come on!
- 维克托 - 走
- Victor! - Come on!
我们不能抛下他
We can't leave him.
里德 我们得走了 快
Reed, we got to go now. Come on!
快 快走
Come on. Come on.
- 动作快点 - 快走!
- Come on! - Come on!
走 走 走!
Go go go!
快走 里德! 快跑!
Move your ass, Reed! Move it!
别停
Keep moving!
快走 快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
里德 启动飞行器
Reed, let's go!
好!
Okay!
里德 快啊
Reed, come on!
回程系统不运转了 我不知道该怎么办
The re-entry's not working, I don't know what to do!
赶快让我们走啊
Get us out of here!
里德 快想想办法 我们要回去
Reed do something, we got to go!
- 你们能听到我吗 - 苏
- Guys can you here me? - Sue!
苏 苏 能听到我吗
Sue! Sue, can you hear me?
约翰尼
Johnny!
你们知道自己闯了多大的祸吗
Do you have any idea how much trouble you're in?
是 是 我知道 苏 听着
Yes, yes, I do. Sue, listen.
我需要你手动重载返程系统 好吗
I need you to manually override the re-entry, okay?
好的 好的 我知道了
Okay. Okay, I got it.
- 手动重载返程系统 - 我正在试
- Manually override the re-entry! - I'm trying!
苏 放手一搏
Sue, just do it!
里德 这个门 我关不上门了
Reed, the door! I can't close the door!
- 本 - 这门关不上
- Ben! - The door won't close!
本
Ben?
Ben.
约翰尼
Johnny.
- 里德 - 本
- Reed! - Ben.
- 来... - 本
- Come... - Ben
- 救救我 - 我来了
- help me! - I'm coming!
里德 快帮我
Reed, help me.
我动不了
I can't move.
本
Ben.
你在哪
Where are you?
里德
Reed.
本
Ben.
里德 快帮帮我 我不能动了
Reed, help me. I can't move.
我会把你从这救出去的
I'll get you out of there.
我的天
Oh my god.
区位分类 五十七区
测量血压
Get a BP reading.
骨密度
Bone density?
里德
Reed.
你的手能动吗
Can you move your hand?
本呢
Where is Ben?
继续尝试 里德
Keep trying Reed.
你们知道我的朋友们都在哪吗
Hey. Do you guys know where my friends are?
- 你的食指能动么? - 我 我...
- Can you lift your index finger? - I... I...
我正在努力
I'm trying.
本在哪
Where's Ben?
你们看见他了么 他被压在石头下面了
Did you see him? He was covered in the rocks.
你们为什么不回答我
Why won't you answer me?
我的朋友们呢
Where are my friends?
帮帮我
Help me!
镇静剂增加到五十毫升
Increase sedative 50 CCs.
你们对我做什么了
What have you guys done to me?
那么 事先郑重申明
So, just for the record.
这个项目是由你监管的　对嘛
This program was under your supervision, was it not?
我已经告诉过你 确实是由我监管
但是事情发生的时候我并不在场
I already told you it was, but I wasn't there when it happened.
我只想知道我的孩子们在哪
All I want to know is where are my children.
我要确定他们是否还活着
I need to know if they're alive.
她还不省人事
She's unconscious.
不知为何她一直时隐时现
Somehow she's shifting in and out of the visible spectrum.
我们也不知道怎么回事
We don't know how.
她的体征很平稳
Her vitals are stable.
她似乎自己也控制不了它
She doesn't seem to be able to control it.
似乎有反应了
Looks like we have some activity.
爸
Dad!
我的孩子... 天呐
Son... Oh my god.
救我 里德
Help me, Reed!
救救我
Please, help me.
来人啊
Somebody, please.
有人在吗
Is anybody there?
本
Ben?
来人啊
Somebody, please.
救救我
Help me!
能听到我吗
Can anyone hear me?
请救救我
Please, help me.
救救我
Help.
有人能回答我吗
Somebody answer me.
有人吗
Anybody.
本
Ben?
Ben!
里德
Reed?
老天
Oh my god.
- 本 - 里德 我... 我发生了什么
- Ben. - Reed. What... What happened to me?
我不知道 但我会搞清楚的
I don't know, but I'm going to figure this out.
本
Ben!
拜托 救救我 里德!
Please. Help me, Reed!
一号实验品逃走了 一号实验品...
Subject 1 has escaped containment. Subject 1...
哦 该死 该死 该死
Oh shit. Shit. Shit.
本 本 我会回来找你的 我保证
Ben. Ben. I'm coming back for you, I promise.
不 不 别走 里德 里德 救我
No... no... no. Reed... Reed help me
- 不要丢下我 - 我很抱歉
- Please don't leave me! - I'm Sorry.
里德 求你快做些什么
Reed, do something please!
他在哪  里德在哪
Where is he? Where is Reed?
我不知道
I don't know.
他吓坏了 哈维 他们只是一群受到惊吓的孩子
He's scared, Harvey. They're all just scared kids.
我们现在还不知道他们到底是什么
We don't know what they are right now.
只知道他们都很危险 都有某种非凡的能力
All we know is that they are dangerous and powerful.
而这些对这里的管理层来说具有非凡价值
Which makes them extremely valuable to the guys who run this place.
如果你觉得
If you think for a minute that I'm going to
我会让你把这些孩子变成...
allow you to turn these kids into some kind of...
你别无选择 富兰克林 我也一样
You don't have a choice Franklin, and neither do I.
除非和政府合作 否则谁也不知道这些孩子会变成什么样
Either we play ball with the government, or who knows what happens to those kids.
现在
Now.
我们只能这么办
Here's how this is going to go.
那么你就是本·格林姆
So you're Ben Grimm.
里德在哪
Where's Reed?
我无法想象你们都经历了什么
I can't begin to imagine what you are going through.
他说他会治好我的
He said he'll fix it.
里德在哪
Where is Reed?
里德走了 你的朋友不会回来了
Reed's gone, and your friend isn't coming back.
听着 我知道你很害怕
Look. I know you're scared.
人之常情
You should be.
但是我们会帮你
But we can help you.
你想要治好它么
You want to find a cure?
我们有拥有全世界最好的专家团队
We have resources here, the best in the world.
我们正在分析发生在你身上的情况
We're analyzing what happened to you.
不管它是什么 我们都会找到解决它的办法
Whatever it is, we can find a way to reverse it.
我们可以帮你的 本
We can help you, Ben.
但你也得帮帮我们
But you need to help us, too.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
一年后
在过去的一年中他达到了史无前例的战斗力
His combat effectiveness this past year has been unprecedented.
从预见性来讲 你们已经知道他在战场上能做什么了
In terms of potential, you already know what he's accomplished in the field.
他在秘密行动中百战百胜
He's been active in covert operations with a 100% success rate,
在战场上保护了我们的战士 挽救了无数的生命
protecting our men and women in battle, and saving countless lives.
女士们先生们 这仅仅是个开始
Ladies and gentlemen, this is only the beginning.
巴克斯特事故中其他的幸存者都显示出了独一无二的生理状况
The other survivors of the Baxter incident all exhibited unique physical conditions.
我们研发的套装 可以让他们接纳并控制这些生理状况
We developed suits which allow them to contain and control these conditions.
这位的套装可以控制她的光谱耀斑和折射可见性
This subject's suit controls her spectral flares and refractive visibility.
在注意力极度集中的状态下 她还可以
With intense concentration, she's also developed
使其他物体隐形
the ability to render other objects invisible.
甚至还可以产生冲击波
And to neuropathically produce force fields.
所有这些能力来自同一个地方
All these abilities come from one place,
一个被我们的科学家称之为零星球的另一维空间
another dimension that our scientists have taken to calling Planet Zero,
正是这个星球的能量转变了这些幸存者
a planet infused with the same energy that transformed these survivors
它同样也具备改变我们的军事能力的潜在性
and potentially could transform our military capabilities.
这就是我们发现的直接联系
We have the direct link.
在你们的支持下 一旦二号量子门工程完成
With your continued support, once the Quantum Gate 2 project is finished,
我们能控制的就不仅仅只是地球了
we'll have control over more than that world,
而是整个宇宙
we'll have control over ours.
各位 快看
Everyone, have a look.
那是什么鬼啊
What the hell is that?
二号研究对象
Subject number 2.
六秒内飞了两千米 刷新记录了
Two thousand meters in 6 seconds. New record.
还在练习起飞 我能把它缩到五秒
Still work on my takeoff, I can make it in 5.
所有的目标靶机都消灭掉了
All target drones neutralized.
尽量屏住你的呼吸 苏珊
Keep holding your breath Susan as long as you can.
方向稳定性是33/10 上升稳定 航向倾角八度
Directional stability is 33 over 10, rise is steady, pitch is 8 degrees.
你的平衡性变好了
Your balance is getting better.
嗨
Hey.
他们打算让我参加一个项目
They're gonna send me on a project.
像本那样吗
Like Ben?
我们应该用这些能力去做些事情
We should use these powers to do something.
这不是什么能力
They're not powers.
而是具有攻击性的异常生理状况 我们得治好它
They're aggressively abnormal physical conditions that we're gonna fix.
- 你能把火灭了吗 - 就算是吧
- Can you turn that off? - Okay. Alright.
可要是治不好呢
And what if they can't?
如果要花很长时间才能治好呢
What if it takes more time to get it right,
我们可能得花很多年
we could be talking years.
我可不想成为他们的工具
I am not going to be a tool.
- 约翰尼 - 斯坦 准备好了吗
- Johnny. - Stan, you ready?
- 准备好了 - 点火
- Yes we are. - Flame on.
好的 约翰尼 你可以去休息了 苏
Okay Johnny. Thank you Sue.
别忘了 我们在这是为了重回正常的生活
Don't forget, we're here to get our lives back.
实验对象们已经同意与我们合作
The subjects have agreed to cooperate with us
直至我们找到他们能力的来源 治好他们
until we find the source of their powers and potentially, cure them.
不如去看看那个大家伙吧
Why don't we go see the big guy?
你好 本
Hi Ben.
我带了些华盛顿来的朋友来看你
I've got some friends of mine here from Washington D.C. visiting.
你有时间打个招呼吗
You got a second to say hello?
很荣幸见到你 格林姆先生
It's an honor to meet you Mr. Grimm.
我们感激你为我们所做的一切
We appreciate all you're doing for us.
我们有言在先 不是吗
Well that was the deal, right?
那就是量子门了
There she is, the Quantum Gate herself,
我们今天的主角
the star of the show.
富兰克林
Franklin.
让我来为你们介绍富兰克林·斯通
I'd like for you all to meet Franklin Storm,
他是我们这层的管理人员
who is our supervisor here on the floor.
- 你好 先生 - 早上好
- How do you do Sir. - Good morning.
早上好
Good morning.
还要准备多长时间
How long until it's ready?
出过一些状况 不过我们是越来越接近了
Well we've had a few issues but we're getting closer.
每天都更加接近
Closer every day.
好吧 艾伦博士 我们会给你你想要的
All right Dr. Allen. We'll give you what you need.
同时 我们希望能再派些你的实验对象上战场
In the meantime we'd like to put more of your subjects in the field.
二号已经准备好了
Subject 2 is ready to go.
让他准备战斗
Get him ready for combat.
苏珊
Susan!
能和你谈谈吗
Can I have a word with you?
他们要派约翰尼上战场
They're sending Johnny into the field.
你是说他自己想上战场吧
You mean he's sending himself into the field.
唯一阻止他的办法是治好他
The only way to stop him is to cure him.
那就意味着得弄好量子门
And that means finishing the gate.
没有里德我做不到
I can't finish it without Reed.
里德不会回来了
Reed's not coming back.
他抛弃了我们 把我们丢在了这里
He abandoned us, left us here.
他只是害怕了 他并不知道这是什么地方
He was afraid. He didn't know what this place was.
我不敢相信你居然还在替他辩护
I can't believe you're still defending him.
帮我找到他 苏珊
Help me track him down Susan.
他会听你的
He'll listen to you.
我们会再次打开量子门 找到治疗方法结束这一切
We'll reopen the gate, find a cure, end this.
约翰尼是你的弟弟
Johnny's your brother.
他和你一样也不好受
It's never been as easy for him as it has for you.
无论如何 他是家人
And like it or not, he's family.
家人意味着我们要照料彼此
And family means we take care of each other.
我能做些什么
What can I do?
联邦调查局 中央情报局 国家安全局
在很多地方都发现了里德的踪迹
The FBI, CIA, and NSA have blips of Reed here and there.
- 但是他们好像没发现... - 他的行动规律
- But they can't seem to see... - The pattern.
没错 规律
Pattern
他上次被发现是什么时候
Where was he last seen?
三个月前在巴拿马
Three months ago in Panama.
你能查到IP地址吗
Did you get an IP?
一开始他用的是被遗弃的邮箱帐号
Early on he was using some old buried email accounts.
通过卫星信号传送 他藏得挺深的
Bouncing off satellites, he's keeping himself pretty well hidden.
有那么一小会 我们发现了他的踪迹
For a short while we were able to ping him here and there.
在几个网站上发现了他
Caught him on a few sites.
他在找废金属 分批购买
He was looking for scrap metal, buying parts.
- 他从不在网上待太久 - 他有找别的什么东西吗
- Never stayed online that long. - Is he looking for anything else?
他在找他
He was searching for him.
- 给我放点音乐 - 什么
- I'm gonna need some music. - Excuse me?
什么音乐都行 能帮我思考
Any music. It helps me think.
是安全拴老化了 20美金太贵了
我给你10美金吧
我也得给职员付薪水呀
不是20美金就不卖了
再给5美金 帮你修一下提款机
多谢
Gracias.
C p t _ n 3 m 0
[ C p t _ n 3 m 0 ]
尼莫队长
Captain Nemo.
找到他了
That's him.
他在用继电器设置邮件的路由
He's routing his emails through this relay.
- 找到了 - 你做了你该做的
- Got him. - You did what you had to do.
嗨 本
Hi Ben.
我们为你准备了一个新的项目
We've got another project for you.
我想你会喜欢的
I think you're gonna like this one.
空域遭入侵
[AIRSPACE BREACHED]
站住 不许动
Freeze! Do not move!
趴下 趴下
Get down! On the ground!
不许动
Freeze!
我的天 本
Oh my god Ben.
原来你一直都躲在这
So this is where you been hiding out.
等一下 听我解释
Wait, stop. Okay let me explain.
- 为什么 - 对你或所有人来说 我都不是好消息
- Why? - I'm no good to you, to anyone.
- 这都是我的错 - 那倒是没错
- This is all my fault. - That we can agree on.
疼吗
Does it hurt?
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你离开的时候也是这么说的
That's what you said when you left.
我会让一切好起来的
I'm going to fix this.
你做不到的
You can't fix this.
没人能做到
Nobody can.
我向你保证 我会治好我们的
I promise you, I'm going to fix this.
我早就不再相信你的废话了
I stopped believing in your bullshit a long time ago.
你是我最好的朋友
You were my best friend.
看着我
Look at me.
我不再是你朋友了
I'm not your friend.
是你把我变成了现在这幅鬼样子
You turned me into something else.
做得好 本
Nice work Ben.
嘿 里德
Hey Reed.
对不起 可我别无选择
Look I'm sorry but I didn't have a choice.
我们需要你帮我们弄好量子门
We need your help to finish the gate.
这是我们弄清楚我们的身体状况并解决问题的唯一选择
It's the only chance we have to figure out what happened to us and reverse it.
你真以为他们在乎我们吗
You really think that they care about us?
你知道他们是怎么利用本的
You know how they've used Ben.
是
Yeah.
我知道
I do.
如果我们不阻止他们的话 他们会对约翰尼做出同样的事来
And they're gonna do the same thing to Johnny if we don't stop them.
量子门的那一边是我们的唯一机会
The only shot we've got is on the other side of that gate.
你可曾想过 要是你那天没去科技展览
Do you ever wonder what life would've been like
生活会是什么样子
if you hadn't come to the science fair that day?
我们无法改变过去
We can't change the past.
但我们可以改变未来
But we can change the future.
你说过 你希望你的努力会有所建树
You said you wanted your work to make a difference.
这就是啊
This is it.
这就是你的机会
This is your chance.
准备好了吗
You ready?
你把它弄得真丑
You made it ugly.
很高兴再次见到你 孩子
It's good to see you again son.
给我十分钟时间
I'm gonna need ten minutes.
拿来做什么
To do what?
我需要给源代码做些调整
I need to make a couple adjustments to the source code,
你有些步骤不太对
you have a few steps that are out of order.
不可能就这么简单
It can't be that simple.
估计是要不了十分钟的
It might not be ten minutes, could be a little less.
走吧
Come on, let's go.
我感觉状态不错 斯坦 我这次五秒就能搞定
I got a good feeling Stan, I'm gonna crack 5 seconds.
我能和我儿子待一会吗
Hey could I take a couple minutes with my son?
当然可以
Sure, no problem.
大家暂停五分钟
Guys can you give us 5 minutes.
怎么了
What's going on?
里德回来了 我们现在更加接近了
Reed is back. We're closer than we've ever been before.
接近什么
Closer to what?
我们过去的生活
Our old lives.
- 你是说你的生活 - 不是的 儿子
- Oh you mean your life. - No son.
你总是说我有做大事的潜力
You always said I had the potential to do something important.
我现在做的就是啊
Who's to say this isn't it?
有时候 事情发生是有原因的
Sometimes things just happen for a reason.
约翰尼 你根本不知道他们打算对你做什么
Johnny you have no idea what they are planning to do to you.
不是他们对我做什么
They're not doing anything to me.
是我和他们在共事
I'm doing this with them.
约翰尼 你得听我说
Johnny you need to listen to me.
我就是听了你的话才落到现在这个地步
I did listen to you and that's what got me here in the first place.
我是成年人
I'm an adult.
我能自己做决定
I'm old enough to make my own decisions.
准备发射
Clear for launch.
待命
Stand by.
看看这是谁啊
Look who it is.
嘿
Hey.
- 见到你真高兴 哥们 - 我也是
- It's good seeing you man. - Good to see you too.
声波投影仪准备好了
Sonic projectors engaged.
戴上护目镜
Goggles up.
开始发射
Initiating launch.
系统检查完成 可视图像正常
Systems check complete. We have a visual.
- 控制台收到 - 你收到大气资料了吗
- Roger that control. - Are you receiving atmospheric data?
收到
Copy that.
检查配置
Checking configuration.
数据传输似乎很通畅
Data transmission looks good.
地貌变了
The landscape's changed.
怎么变了
How?
我不知道 就是不太一样了
I don't know, it's just different.
开始进行元素及地质检测
Commencing element, geological test series.
收到
Copy.
控制台 我在大约六十码外捕捉到了热感信号
Hey control, I'm picking up a heat signature about 60 yards away.
会是什么东西
Now what could that be?
很难辨认 信号一直在波动
Hard to make out. The signal keeps fluctuating.
它正在向我们移动
It's moving, heading towards us.
收到 小心前进
Copy that. Proceed with caution.
有图像吗
Do you have a visual?
看起来是人形
It appears to be a human form
周围有一些外星元素
with some sort of foreign element around it.
我就知道你们会回来的
I knew you would come back.
- 维克托 - 不可能
- Victor? - Not possible.
看起来是受伤了
Subject appears injured.
- 快拿急救包 - 快把他弄上飞船
- Get the med kit. - Let's get him to the shuttle.
- 好了 放松点 伙计们 – 快点
- Alright, easy guys. - Come on.
任务终止 把他带回来
Abort. Bring him back.
- 终止任务 稳定目标 – 哦 该死
- Aborting mission. Stabilizing the subject. - Oh, shit.
准备传输
Prepare to transport.
准备起飞
Preparing for launch.
将他转移至第一密封舱
Transfer the subject to containment room 1.
收到
Copy that.
他的热感信号几乎探测不到
His thermal signature is barely registering.
他的生化指标非常高
His biochemistry is off the charts.
我想和他谈谈
I want to talk to him.
在我和他谈话之前 谁也不许和他交流
Nobody talks to him until I do.
其他人都留在岗位上
Confine the others to their quarters.
维克托
Victor?
我们还不知道你是怎么在那里活下来的
We don't know how you survived over there but...
我们还在分析数据
we're still analyzing the data.
看起来就好像是...
It appears as if...
你的防护服和你的身体融在一起了
environment suit fused with your body but
但我们会想出解决办法的
we're working on that.
我们会帮你的 维克托
We're going to help you, Victor.
我们现在和政府合作了
We're working with the government now.
我们要接着去另一边探索
We're going to send more expeditions to the other side
但首先你得告诉我们你所知道的一切关于那里的信息
but first, you need to tell us everything you know about that place.
你想知道我是怎么活下来的吗
You want to know how I survived?
就是那个地方让我活下来的
That place kept me alive.
它给了我力量
Gave me strength,
还有能力
power.
什么样的能力
What kind of power?
像你这样的人永远也无法拥有的能力
The kind men like you must never possess.
你会忍不住想要回来
You couldn't resist coming back.
毁掉你的世界轻而易举
It's not enough to ruin your world.
而你却想毁掉我的
Now you want to ruin mine.
维克托
Victor.
如果毁灭这个世界 我的世界才有可能留下的话
If this world must die so that mine may live,
那就毁掉吧
so be it.
红色警戒
Code Red.
发生紧急事态
There is an emergency in this building.
执行标准紧急程序
Follow standard emergency protocols.
立刻从最近的出口离开建筑物
Proceed to the nearest exit and leave the building immediately.
红色警戒 红色警戒
Code Red. Code Red.
发生紧急事态
There is an emergency in this building.
我们得出去
Get to the outside!
- 快点 快走 – 从这儿走
- Hurry! Go! Go! - Over here.
红色警戒 红色警戒
Code Red. Code Red.
发生紧急事态
There is an emergency in this building.
执行标准紧急程序
Follow standard emergency protocols.
立刻从最近的出口离开建筑物
Proceed to the nearest exit and leave the building immediately.
你又要临阵脱逃吗
Running away again?
不
No.
苏
Sue!
抱歉 你还好吗
My bad, are you okay?
没事 我还好
Yeah. I'm all right.
爸爸在哪儿
Where's dad?
维克托 不要 快停下
Victor, no. Just stop!
别挡道 富兰克林 我要回家去
Out of my way, Franklin. I'm going home.
这儿就是你的家 小子
This is your home, son.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
那里没有你想要的东西
There's nothing for you over there.
只有创造新世界的力量
Only the power to create a new world.
维克托 我们不是上帝
Victor, we're not gods.
我们只是普通人
We're just people.
我们在一起会比分开的时候更有力量
And we are stronger together than we are apart.
你孤身一人有什么好处
What good is it if you're alone?
我一直是孤身一人
I have always been alone.
维克托 住手
Victor, stop!
快住手
Just stop!
太迟了 苏珊
It's too late, Susan.
地球就要毁灭了
The earth is dying.
人类自己放弃了机会
Humanity had it's chance.
- 不 - 爸爸
- No! - Dad!
爸爸 不
Dad! No!
- 爸爸 不要 对不起 – 爸爸 不
- Dad, no. I'm Sorry! - Dad, no!
爸爸
Dad.
- 不 – 爸爸
- No! - Dad!
爸爸 醒醒
Dad, move.
维克托 住手
Victor, no!
答应我
Promise me.
你们要照顾好彼此
Look after each other.
爸爸 对不起 爸爸 对不起
Dad, I'm sorry. Dad, I'm sorry.
不
No.
他在让系统超负荷运行 来造成失控反应
He's overloading the system to create a runaway reaction.
那会停不下来的
It's not going to stop.
它会制造出黑洞 然后把地球吞噬
It'll create a black hole that'll swallow the earth.
它会把一切都拉到另一个维度里去
It's pulling everything into the other dimension.
坚持住
Hold on!
约翰尼
Johnny!
明白
Got it.
地球上的物质正在转化成能量
The matter from Earth is being converted to energy.
我们得阻止维克托 他是一切的源头
We need to stop Victor, he's the source.
我来对付他
He's mine.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
我要上了
This is what I do.
你在哪儿 苏珊
Where are you Susan?
维克托 别这么做
Victor, don't do this!
维克托已经不存在了
There is no Victor.
现在只有杜姆
There is only Doom.
我看见了不一样的未来 苏珊
I saw a different future for us, Susan.
帮帮我
Help me!
里德
Reed!
本
Ben.
再见了 苏珊
Goodbye, Susan.
里德
Reed!
他死了吗
Is he dead?
如果那玩意还是活跃状态 那他就也还活着
If that thing's still active, so is he.
我们没法击败他 他比我们任何一个都更强
We can't beat him. He's stronger than any of us.
确实如此 但他并不比我们所有人加起来还要强
Yeah, he is. But he's not stronger than all of us.
这个地方可以赋予他力量
Look, this place gave him his powers.
但是也同样给了我们力量
But it gave us all of ours too.
这就是我们现在的样子
It's who we are now.
也许我们注定要成为这样的人
Maybe it's who we're meant to be.
是我们打开的这扇门 就得由我们来关上
We opened this door, we're gonna close it.
那计划是什么
So what's the plan?
够了
Enough!
等到你们的世界全部毁灭 只剩下我一个的时候
When your world is destroyed and I'm all that's left
那才会让我满意
then, it will be enough.
你总是这么自以为是 觉得自己比我聪明
Always so smug, thinking you were smarter than me.
我本来就比你聪明
I am smarter than you.
就是现在
Now!
吃我一拳
Hey! It's clobberin' time!
这最好能有用
This better work.
不
NO!
我们快离开这个鬼地方
Let's get the hell outta here!
虽然这个世界并不知道你们为了拯救它做了什么
While the world may not know what you did to save it,
但是在这个房间里的人知道
the men and the women in this room do.
总统也知道
And so does the president.
也就是说 我们愿意维持现在的关系
That said, we'd like to continue our existing relationship.
那么
So
- 我们达成一致了吗 - 并没有
- If we're all in agreement? - We're not.
抱歉 你说什么
Excuse me?
我们并没有达成一致
We're not remotely all in agreement.
我们不需要你或者其他的什么人监视我们
We don't need you or anybody else to keep an eye on us.
我们只想要一个工作的空间
We just want a place where we can work.
而且我们取得的成果都属于我们自己
And whatever we come up with belongs to us.
如果我们拒绝呢
And what if we say no?
你们没权利拒绝
Say yes.
你们想要多少空间
How much space are we talking about?
很大
A lot.
好吧
So.
我本来以为会是你们四个一起来
I thought there were going to be four of you.
哦 马上就到
Oh, there is.
实验室在楼上
Labs are upstairs,
工程室在南边
engineering's on the south side and
装配车间在楼下
and assembly's downstairs.
严格来讲 我们已经在这儿工作
We've been operating out of here for
超过十二年了
over 12 years now. Well, officially, that is.
但是你们不会在任何政府文书里找到我们的名字
But you still won't find our name on any government books.
大部分人还是会把这儿看成... 中心城市
Most people just refer to this as... Central City.
随便怎么叫吧 我们现在为你们工作了
But call it whatever you want. We work for you now.
- 这才像样 - 真棒
- Now that's what I'm talking about. - That looks pretty nice.
那一块区域我要了
I'm taking that area over there.
我会习惯的
I could get used to this.
我想到了
I got it.
这个地方就叫富兰克林·斯通 研究中心
The Franklin Storm Research Center.
爸爸对用他的名字命名不太适应
Dad was kind of allergic to his name in big letters.
我突然想到 我们四个也应该有个名字
Which reminds me, I think that the four of us should have a name.
我们为什么要起名字
Why would we need a name?
因为我们现在是一个团队了 团队里有我们四个
Because we're a team now, and there's four of us.
所以我们应该给这个团队起个名字
So, we should come up with a name for it.
我喜欢 "人类火炬和女火炬" 这个名字
I like "The Human Torch and the Torchettes."
- 呃 - 不要
- Ugh. - No.
你在逗我吗
You kidding me?
那"超级大脑和他的神经元" 怎么样
How about "The Big Brain and his Neurons?"
那怎么不叫"超级大脑和她的神经元"
How about "The Big Brain and her Neurons?"
叫"两男一女和一个谁都嫌弃的东西" 怎么样
How about "Two guys, a girl, and the Thing that nobody wanted?"
嘿 我们知道你不会把那放在心上的
Hey. We both know that you could take him.
- 嘿 - 嘿 怎么了
- Hey! - Hey, what?
我们从车库一路走来经历得真不少
We've come a long way since the garage.
我得说 真是太神奇了
I gotta say. It's fantastic.
再说一遍
Say that again?
真是太神奇了
It's fantastic.
没错 就是这个
Yes, it is.
我知道该起什么名字了
Guys, I got it.
- 准备好了吗 – 好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
神奇四侠
FANTASTIC FOUR
四
[4]